The Peter Bekker Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 1. Peter Bekker, Jr.
  - Subseries 1.10 Ephemera
    - Subseries 1.10.2 Magnets
      - Hadirans Wall magnet (Box 22, Compartment 4)
      - English telephone box magnet (Box 22, Compartment 4)
      - English postbox magnet (Box 22, Compartment 4)
      - Plane magnet (Box 22, Compartment 4)
      - Plane magnet (Box 22, Compartment 4)
      - Plane magnet (Box 22, Compartment 4)
      - Plane magnet (Box 22, Compartment 4)
      - Dog magnet (Box 22, Compartment 4)
      - Einstein magnet (Box 22, Compartment 4)
      - Code 3 magnet (Box 22, Compartment 5)
      - Fly to Alaska (Box 22, Compartment 5)
      - Golden State Birdge (Box 22, Compartment 5)
      - Gargoyle magnet (Box 22, Compartment 6)
      - Gargoyle magnet (Box 22, Compartment 7)
      - Wolf magnet (Box 22, Compartment 8)
      - Wagon wheel and cow skull magnet (Box 22, Compartment 9)
      - Vintage car magnet (Box 25)
    - Subseries 1.10.3 Buttons
      - A
      - B
      - C
      - D
      - E
      - F
      - G
      - H
      - J
      - M
      - N
      - R
      - S
      - T
      - U
      - Unlabelled
    - Subseries 1.10.4 Awards
      - Microsoft Ship It Award (Box 25)
      - MSN Investors Plaque (Box 25)
    - Subseries 1.10.5 Microphones
      - WCBS 88 News Microphone Stand (Box 25)
      - News 88 Microphone Stand and Headphones (Box 25)
      - Box with microphone and wire (Box 25)
      - The New York Press Club Box (Box 25)
    - Subseries 1.10.6 Mugs
      - Chicago Tribune mug (Box 25)
      - Elektra Asylum Mug (Box 25)
      - Decision 76 Mug (Box 25)
      - MSN The Microsoft Network Mug (Box 25)
    - Subseries 1.10.7 Misc. Objects
      - High Grade Sharps, Das Co [Packet of sewing needles (Box 23, Compartment 11)
      - Matchbox, Family Britches (Box 23, Compartment 11)
      - Earings (Box 23, Compartment 11)
      - CNN lanyard (Box 23, Compartment 11)
      - Champagn Cork, Between the Lines 4-1-81 (Box 24, Compartment 1)
      - Stopwatch (Box 24, Compartment 2)
      - Stopwatch (Box 24, Compartment 3)
      - Stopwatch (Box 24, Compartment 4)
      - Beatles wrist watch (Box 24, Compartment 5)
      - Keys (Box 24, Compartment 6)
      - Clapboard (Box 21)
      - Notepads, The Tourists Luminous Basement on Epic Records & Tapes (x2) (Box 21)
      - Edison Blue Amberol Record (Box 21)
      - Edison Blue Amberol Record (Box 21)
- 2. Peter Bekker, Sr., 0.75 linear feet 1 Box
  - Subseries 2.1 Far East Network
    - Closed Circuit Operational Television Study (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Closed Circuit Television Proposals (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - FEN Programming Planning Documents (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Newspaper Clippings: FEN Programming and News, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Newspaper Clippings: FEN Programming and News, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Newspaper Clippings: FEN Programming and News, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Newspaper Clippings: FEN Programming and News, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Newspaper Clippings: FEN Programming and News, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Newspaper Clippings: FEN Programming and News, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper Clippings: FEN Programming and News, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper Clippings: FEN Programming and News, Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - [Oversized] Newspaper Clippings: FEN Programming and News, 1956-1962 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      See Oversized Box, Folder 2.1.28.7
    - Formal Writing on FEN, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 2.2 Military Documents
    - Personnel Records, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Personnel Records, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Personnel Records, 1947-1949 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Personnel Records, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Personnel Records, 1952-1955 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Personnel Records, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Personnel Records, 1957-1959 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Personnel Records, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Personnel Records, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Personnel Records, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Personnel Records, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Personnel Records, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Personnel Records, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Personnel Records, 1697 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Personnel Records, 1968-1971, Undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Flight Records, 1944-1949 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Flight Records, 1950-1954 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Flight Records, 1955-1969 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Military Accomplishments (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - [Oversized] Military Awards and Accomplishments (Box 7, Folder 25)
      See Oversized Box, Folder 2.2.28.8
    - Newspaper Clippings from Military Career (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Speech Drafts (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Subseries 2.3 Correspondence
    - Correspondence, 1952-1959 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1960-1969 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1972, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 2.4 Personal Materials
    - Education Certificates, 1936-1951 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Education Records, 1941-1978 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Grade Slips, 1957-1960 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Resume and Personal Background Statements, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Dressage Competition, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Aviation Ground Systems Patent, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 2.5 Paul W. Bekker
    - [Oversized] Extractus Document, 1912 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      See Oversized Box, Folder 2.2.25.8
    - Passport, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Estate of Paul W. Bekker, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 2.6 Miscellany
    - Materials found with photographs (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 2.7 Photographs
    - Subseries 2.7.1. Far East Network Photos
      - Slides, Belgium Far East Network (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Photographic Prints, Ehtopia, Far East Network, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Slides, England, Far East Network, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Slides, Europe, Far East Network (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Photographic Prints, France, FEN, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Slides, France, FEN, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Photographic Prints, Germany, FEN, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Slides, Germany, FEN (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Photographic Prints, Greece, Far East Network, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Photographic Prints, Iran, Far East Network, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Japan, Far East Network (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Photographic Prints, Pakistan, FEN, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Photographic Prints, Saidi Arabia, FEN, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Photographic Prints, Turkey, FEN, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - FEN Presentation Slides (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Subseries 2.7.2 Military Photos
      - Military Awards (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Military Photos (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Film, Air Force (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Subseries 2.7.3 Personal Photos
      - Historical Family Photographs (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - Peter Bekker Sr. Childhood Photos (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - Family and Historical Photos (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Family and Historical Photos (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Family Photos, Film (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Thornwood, Slides (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - Photo Wallet (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Family Photos (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Subseries 2.7.4 Personal Photos, Japan
      - Film (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Japan, May-58 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Japan, June - July, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Japan, August - September, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Trips Around Japan, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Trips Around Japan (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Photos From Around Tokyo (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Personal Photos from Japan (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Family Photos from Japan (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Party Photos in Japan (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Japanese Landscape (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Subseries 2.7.5 Dessage Competitions
      - Scrapbook #1 Photos (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Scrapbook #2 Photos (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Polace Horse Show, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Dressage Slides, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 2.8 Ephemera
    - Subseries 2.8.1 Military Ribbons/Pins (Box 24, Compartment 7)
      - American Campaign (Box 24, Compartment 8)
      - Carbine (Box 24, Compartment 9)
      - Efficiency Honor Difelity (Box 24, Compartment 10)
      - European Africcan Middle Eastern Campaign (Box 24, Compartment 11)
      - World War II (Box 24, Compartment 12)
      - Honorable Service, label button (Box 24, Compartment 13)
    - Subseries 2.8.2 Clothing
      - Letter Jacket (Box 29)
      - World War II Bomber Jacket (Box 29)
    - Subseries 2.8.3 Misc. Ephemera
      - Kodak Camera Ring Adaptor, with box (Box 24, Compartment 14)